Finding Aid for William D. Ford Papers 1955-1995
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Subject Files 1965-1995, 79 linear feet
  - 1978-1979
    - Ford [William D.] Vocational-Technical Center (Box 26)
    - Gasoline Deregulation (Box 26)
    - Government Regulations (Box 26)
    - Government Spending (Box 26)
    - Gun Control (Box 26)
    - Health Care (Box 26)
    - Hospitals (Box 26)
    - Housing and Urban Development, Department of (Box 26)
    - Inflation (Box 26)
    - Interior Department (Box 26)
    - Internal Revenue Service (Box 26)
    - Interstate Commerce Commission (Box 26)
    - Iran (Box 26)
    - Irish Congressional Caucus (Box 26)
    - Juvenile Delinquency (Box 26)
    - Labor Department (Box 26)
    - Lobbyists (Box 26)
    - Marijuana (Box 26)
    - Mass Transit (Box 26)
    - Mental Health (Box 26)
    - Metric System (Box 26)
    - Michigan Department of Social Services (Box 26)
    - Michigan State Legislature (Box 26)
    - Middle East (Box 26)
    - Military (Box 26)
    - Miscellaneous Constituent Correspondence (Box 26)
    - Mortgage Bonds (Box 26)
    - Municipal Bonds (Box 26)
    - National Health Insurance (Box 26)
    - Nuclear Regulatory Commission (Box 26)
    - Nursing (Box 26)
    - Nursing Homes (Box 26)
    - Older Americans Act (Box 26)
    - Panama Canal (Box 26)
    - Patronage (Box 27)
    - Pension Plan Merger (Box 27)
    - Pointe Moullee (Box 27)
    - Pornography (Box 27)
    - Postal Service (Box 27)
    - Prison Reform (Box 27)
    - Questionnaire Replies (Box 27)
    - Railroads (Box 27)
    - Religious Discrimination (Box 27)
    - Rockwood Prison (Box 27)
    - Russian Troops (Box 27)
    - Saccharin (Box 27)
    - SALT Treaty (Box 27)
    - School Prayer (Box 27)
    - Senior Citizens (Box 27)
    - Small Business (Box 27)
    - Social Security (Box 27)
    - Social Security Administration Proposals (Box 27)
    - Soviet Human Rights (Box 27)
    - State Department (Box 27)
    - Steel Caucus (Box 27)
    - Steering and Policy Committee (Box 27)
    - Survey Code (Box 27)
    - Taiwan (Box 27)
    - Tax Reform (Box 27)
    - Trade (Box 27)
    - Trade Reform (Box 27)
    - Transportation (Box 27)
    - Treasury Department (Box 27)
    - Trucking (Box 27)
    - Trucking Deregulation (Box 27)
    - Unanswered Mail (Box 27)
    - Unidentified Flying Objects (Box 27)
    - Van Buren Township (Box 27)
    - Veterans Benefits (Box 27)
    - Wayne State University (Box 27)
    - Welfare (Box 27)
  - 1979-1980
    (Subject Files for this year were received in 1997, files prior to Energy not received)
    - Energy (Box 150)
      - General (Box 150)
      - Coal (Box 150)
      - Conservation (Box 150)
      - Dept. of (Box 150)
      - Gasohol (Box 150)
      - Low income assistance (Box 150)
      - Newsletter (responses to) (Box 150)
      - Standby conservation plan (Box 150)
      - Synthetic fuel (Box 150)
      - Windfall profits tax (Box 150)
    - Environmental Protection Agency (Box 150)
    - Federal Communications Commission (Box 150)
    - Federal Reserve Board (Box 150)
    - Federal Trade Commission (Box 150)
    - Flood (Box 150)
    - Food Stamps (Box 150)
    - Food Stamps for strikers (1972-1978) (Box 150)
    - Ford, William D. (correspondence and clipping) (Box 150)
    - Foreign affairs (Box 150)
    - General Motors, Detroit Diesel Allison Division (1975) (Box 150)
    - Great Lakes (Box 150)
    - Health, Education, and Welfare, Dept. of (Box 150)
    - Housing (Box 150)
    - Housing and Urban Development, Dept. of (Box 150)
    - Inflation (Box 150)
    - Interior Dept. (Box 150)
    - Internal Revenue Service (Box 150)
    - Labor Dept. (Box 150)
    - Law Enforcement Assistance Administration (Box 150)
    - League of Women Voters of Michigan (Box 150)
    - Medicare (Box 150)
    - Michigan Unemployment Insurance (Box 150)
    - Military draft (Box 150)
    - MX missile (Box 150)
    - Nicaragua (Box 150)
    - Nuclear Regulatory Commission (Box 150)
    - Nuclear waste (Box 150)
    - Oil import fee (Box 150)
    - Pension plan merger (Box 150)
    - Project ELF (Box 150)
    - Questionnaires results replies (Box 150)
    - Revenue sharing (Box 150)
    - School prayer (Box 150)
    - Selective Service (Box 150)
    - Senior citizens (Box 150)
    - Social Security (Box 151)
    - Steering and Policy Committee (Box 151)
    - Storm aid (Box 151)
    - Super sewer (Box 151)
    - Superfund (Box 151)
    - Tax reform (Box 151)
    - Telegrams sent (Box 151)
    - Thank yous received from member of Congress (Box 151)
    - Toyota (Box 151)
    - Trade Adjustment Act (Box 151)
    - Truck deregulation (Box 151)
    - Welfare to aliens (Box 151)
    - Windfall profits (Box 151)
  - 1980-1981
    - Abortion (Box 27)
    - Aged (Box 27)
    - Animals (Box 27)
    - Appropriations (Box 27)
    - Banking and Currency (Box 27)
    - Budget (Box 27)
    - Business and Industry (Box 28)
    - Child Nutrition (Box 28)
    - Civil Rights (Box 28)
    - Civil Service (Box 28)
    - Communications (Box 28)
    - Congress (Box 28)
    - Economy (Box 28)
    - Education (Box 28)
    - Energy (Box 29)
    - Environment (Box 29)
    - Fine Arts (Box 29)
    - Foreign Relations (Box 29)
    - Health (Box 29)
    - Housing (Box 29)
    - Immigration (Box 29)
    - Labor (Box 29)
    - Law Enforcement (Box 29)
    - Military (Box 29)
    - Office Administration (Box 29)
    - Political (Box 29)
    - Postal Service (Box 29)
    - Public Relations (Box 29)
    - Public Relations, cont. (Box 30)
    - Science and Technology (Box 30)
    - Social Programs (Box 30)
    - State of Michigan (Box 30)
    - Taxes (Box 30)
    - Transportation (Box 30)
    - Veterans (Box 30)
  - 1982-1983
    - Abortion (Box 31)
    - Aged (Box 31)
    - Agriculture (Box 31)
    - Animals (Box 31)
    - Banking and Currency (Box 31)
    - Budget (Box 31)
    - Business and Industry (Box 31)
    - Child Nutrition (Box 31)
    - Civil Rights (Box 31)
    - Civil Service (Box 31)
    - Commerce (Box 31)
    - Communications (Box 31)
    - Congress (Box 31)
    - Consumer Protection (Box 32)
    - Disasters (Box 32)
    - Economy (Box 32)
    - Education (Box 32)
    - Energy (Box 32)
    - Environment (Box 32)
    - Fine Arts (Box 32)
    - Foreign Relations (Box 32)
    - Health (Box 32)
    - Housing (Box 32)
    - Immigration (Box 32)
    - Labor (Box 32)
    - Law Enforcement (Box 33)
    - Military (Box 33)
    - Political (Box 33)
    - Postal Service (Box 33)
    - Public Relations (Box 33)
    - Science and Technology (Box 33)
    - Social Programs (Box 33)
    - State of Michigan (Box 33)
    - Taxes (Box 34)
    - Transportation (Box 34)
    - Veterans (Box 34)
    - White House (Box 34)
  - 1983-1984
    - Abortion (Box 34)
    - Aged (Box 34)
    - Agriculture (Box 34)
    - Animals (Box 34)
    - Banking (Box 34)
    - Budget (Box 34)
    - Business and Industry (Box 34)
    - Civil Rights (Box 34)
    - Commerce (Box 35)
    - Communications (Box 35)
    - Congress (Box 35)
    - Consumer Protection (Box 35)
    - Disasters (Box 35)
    - Economy (Box 35)
    - Energy (Box 35)
    - Environment (Box 35)
    - Foreign Relations (Box 35)
    - Health (Box 36)
    - Housing (Box 36)
    - Immigration (Box 36)
    - Labor (Box 36)
    - Law Enforcement (Box 36)
    - Military (Box 36)
    - Office Administration (Box 36)
    - Political (Box 36)
    - Postal Service (Box 36)
    - Public Relations (Box 36)
    - Public Relations, cont. (Box 37)
    - Science and Technology (Box 37)
    - Social Programs (Box 37)
    - State of Michigan (Box 37)
    - Taxes (Box 37)
    - Transportation (Box 37)
    - Veterans (Box 37)
    - White House (Box 37)
  - 1984-1985
    - Abortion (Box 38)
    - Aged (Box 38)
    - Agriculture (Box 38)
    - Animals (Box 38)
    - Banking and Currency (Box 38)
    - Budget (Box 38)
    - Business and Industry (Box 38)
    - Civil Rights (Box 38)
    - Commerce (Box 38)
    - Communications (Box 38)
    - Congress (Box 38)
    - Consumer Protection (Box 38)
    - Economy (Box 38)
    - Energy (Box 38)
    - Environment (Box 39)
    - Foreign Relations (Box 39)
    - Health (Box 39)
    - Housing (Box 39)
    - Immigration (Box 39)
    - Labor (Box 39)
    - Law Enforcement (Box 39)
    - Military (Box 39)
    - Office Administration (Box 39)
    - Political (Box 39)
    - Postal Service (Box 39)
    - Public Relations (Box 40)
    - Science and Technology (Box 40)
    - Social Programs (Box 40)
    - State of Michigan (Box 40)
    - Taxes (Box 40)
    - Transportation (Box 40)
    - Veterans (Box 40)
    - White House (Box 40)
  - 1985-1986
    - Abortion (Box 40)
    - Aged (Box 40)
    - Agriculture (Box 40)
    - Animals (Box 40)
    - Banking and Currency (Box 40)
    - Budget (Box 40)
    - Business and Industry (Box 41)
    - Civil Rights (Box 41)
    - Commerce (Box 41)
    - Communications (Box 41)
    - Congress (Box 41)
    - Energy (Box 41)
    - Environment (Box 41)
    - Foreign Relations (Box 41)
    - Health (Box 41)
    - Housing (Box 42)
    - Immigration (Box 42)
    - Labor (Box 42)
    - Law Enforcement (Box 42)
    - Military (Box 42)
    - Office Administration (Box 42)
    - Political (Box 42)
    - Public relations (Box 42)
    - Science and Technology (Box 42)
    - Social Programs (Box 42)
    - State of Michigan (Box 42)
    - Taxes (Box 42)
    - Taxes, cont. (Box 43)
    - Transportation (Box 43)
    - Veterans (Box 43)
    - White House (Box 43)
  - 1986-1987
    - Abortion (Box 43)
    - Aged (Box 43)
    - Agriculture (Box 43)
    - Animals (Box 44)
    - Banking (Box 44)
    - Budget (Box 44)
    - Business (Box 44)
    - Civil Rights (Box 44)
    - Civil Service (Box 44)
    - Commerce (Box 44)
    - Communications (Box 44)
    - Congress (Box 44)
    - Disasters (Box 44)
    - Energy (Box 44)
    - Environment (Box 44)
    - Foreign Relations (Box 45)
    - Health (Box 45)
    - Housing (Box 45)
    - Immigration (Box 45)
    - Labor (Box 45)
    - Law Enforcement (Box 45)
    - Military (Box 45)
    - Political (Box 45)
    - Postal Service (Box 45)
    - Public Relations (Box 45)
    - Science and Technology (Box 45)
    - Social Programs (Box 45)
    - State of Michigan (Box 46)
    - Taxes (Box 46)
    - Transportation (Box 46)
    - Veterans (Box 46)
    - White House (Box 46)
  - 1987-1988
    - Abortion (Box 46)
    - Aged (Box 46)
    - Agriculture (Box 46)
    - Animals (Box 46)
    - Banking and Currency (Box 46)
    - Budget (Box 47)
    - Business and Industry (Box 47)
    - Civil Rights (Box 47)
    - Civil Service (Box 47)
    - Commerce (Box 47)
    - Communications (Box 47)
    - Congress (Box 47)
    - Disasters (Box 47)
    - Economy (Box 47)
    - Energy (Box 47)
    - Environment (Box 47)
    - Foreign Relations (Box 47)
    - Health (Box 47)
    - Housing (Box 48)
    - Immigration (Box 48)
    - Labor (Box 48)
    - Law Enforcement (Box 48)
    - Military (Box 48)
    - Politics (Box 48)
    - Public Relations (Box 48)
    - Science and Technology (Box 48)
    - Social Programs (Box 48)
    - State of Michigan (Box 48)
    - Taxes (Box 48)
    - Transportation (Box 49)
    - Veterans (Box 49)
    - White House (Box 49)
  - 1988-1989
    - Abortion (Box 49)
    - Aged (Box 49)
    - Agriculture (Box 49)
    - Animals (Box 49)
    - Banking and Currency (Box 49)
    - Budget (Box 49)
    - Business and Industry (Box 49)
    - Civil Rights (Box 49)
    - Commerce (Box 49)
    - Communications (Box 49)
    - Congress (Box 49)
    - Economy (Box 49)
    - Energy (Box 49)
    - Environment (Box 50)
    - Foreign Relations (Box 50)
    - Health (Box 50)
    - Housing (Box 50)
    - Immigration (Box 50)
    - Labor Law Enforcement (Box 50)
    - Military (Box 50)
    - Political (Box 51)
    - Postal Service (Box 51)
    - Public Relations (Box 51)
    - Science and Technology (Box 51)
    - Social Programs (Box 51)
    - State of Michigan (Box 51)
    - Taxes (Box 51)
    - Transportation (Box 51)
    - Veterans (Box 51)
  - 1989-1990
    - Abortion (Box 51)
    - Agriculture (Box 51)
    - Animals (Box 51)
    - Banking and Currency (Box 51)
    - Budget (Box 51)
    - Business and Industry (Box 51)
    - Civil Rights (Box 51)
    - Commerce (Box 51)
    - Communications (Box 51)
    - Congress (Box 52)
    - Economy (Box 52)
    - Energy (Box 52)
    - Environment (Box 52)
    - Foreign Relations (Box 52)
    - Health (Box 52)
    - Housing (Box 52)
    - Immigration (Box 52)
    - Labor (Box 53)
    - Law Enforcement (Box 53)
    - Military (Box 53)
    - Political (Box 53)
    - Postal Service (Box 53)
    - Public Relations (Box 53)
    - Social Programs (Box 53)
    - State of Michigan (Box 53)
    - Taxes (Box 53)
    - Transportation (Box 53)
    - Veterans (Box 53)
  - 1990-1991
    - Abortion (Box 54)
    - Aged (Box 54)
    - Agriculture (Box 54)
    - Animals (Box 54)
    - Banking and Currency (Box 54)
    - Budget (Box 54)
    - Business and Industry (Box 54)
    - Civil Rights (Box 54)
    - Commerce (Box 54)
    - Communications (Box 54)
    - Congress (Box 54)
    - Economy (Box 54)
    - Energy (Box 54)
    - Environment (Box 54)
    - Environment, cont. (Box 55)
    - Foreign Relations (Box 55)
    - Health (Box 55)
    - House Administration (Box 55)
    - Housing (Box 55)
    - Immigration (Box 55)
    - Labor (Box 55)
    - Labor, cont. (Box 56)
    - Law Enforcement (Box 56)
    - Merchant Marine and Fisheries (Box 56)
    - Military (Box 56)
    - Political (Box 56)
    - Postal Service (Box 56)
    - Public Relations (Box 56)
    - Science and Technology (Box 56)
    - Social Programs (Box 57)
    - State of Michigan (Box 57)
    - Taxes (Box 57)
    - Transportation (Box 57)
    - Veterans (Box 57)
    - White House (Box 57)
  - 1991-1992
    - Abortion (Box 57)
    - Aged (Box 57)
    - Agriculture (Box 57)
    - Animals (Box 57)
    - Banking (Box 57)
    - Budget (Box 57)
    - Business and Industry (Box 57)
    - Commerce (Box 58)
    - Communications (Box 58)
    - Congress (Box 58)
    - Economy (Box 58)
    - Energy (Box 58)
    - Environment (Box 58)
    - Foreign Relations (Box 59)
    - Health (Box 59)
    - Housing (Box 59)
    - Immigration (Box 59)
    - Law Enforcement (Box 59)
    - Law Enforcement, cont. (Box 60)
    - Military (Box 60)
    - Political (Box 60)
    - Public Relations (Box 61)
    - Science and Technology (Box 61)
    - Social Programs (Box 61)
    - State of Michigan (Box 61)
    - Taxes (Box 61)
    - Transportation (Box 61)
    - Veterans (Box 61)
    - White House (Box 61)
  - 1992-1993
    - Abortion (Box 62)
    - Agriculture (Box 62)
    - Animals (Box 62)
    - Banking and Currency (Box 62)
    - Budget (Box 62)
    - Business and Industry (Box 62)
    - Commerce (Box 62)
    - Communications (Box 63)
    - Congress (Box 63)
    - Disasters (Box 63)
    - Economy (Box 63)
    - Energy (Box 63)
    - Environment (Box 63)
    - Foreign Relations (Box 64)
    - Health (Box 64)
    - Housing (Box 65)
    - Immigration (Box 65)
    - Labor (Box 65)
    - Law Enforcement (Box 65)
    - Military (Box 65)
    - Office Administration (Box 65)
    - Political (Box 66)
    - Public Relations (Box 66)
    - Science and Technology (Box 66)
    - Social Programs (Box 66)
    - State of Michigan (Box 66)
    - Taxes (Box 66)
    - Transportation (Box 66)
    - Transportation, cont. (Box 67)
    - Veterans (Box 67)
  - 1993-1994
    - Abortion (Box 67)
    - Agriculture (Box 67)
    - Animals (Box 67)
    - Banking (Box 67)
    - Budget (Box 68)
    - Business and Industry (Box 68)
    - Commerce (Box 68)
    - Communications (Box 68)
    - Congress (Box 68)
    - Disasters (Box 68)
    - Education and Labor (Box 69)
    - Energy (Box 69)
    - Environment (Box 69)
    - Foreign Relations (Box 70)
    - Health (Box 70)
    - Housing (Box 71)
    - Immigration (Box 71)
    - Judiciary (Box 71)
    - Military (Box 71)
    - Military, cont. (Box 72)
    - Political (Box 72)
    - Public Relations (Box 72)
    - Science and Technology (Box 72)
    - State of Michigan (Box 72)
    - Taxes (Box 72)
    - Taxes, cont. (Box 73)
    - Transportation (Box 73)
    - Veterans (Box 73)
  - 1994-1995
    - Abortion (Box 73)
    - Agriculture (Box 73)
    - Animals (Box 73)
    - Banking (Box 73)
    - Budget (Box 73)
    - Business and Industry (Box 73)
    - Commerce (Box 74)
    - Communications (Box 74)
    - Congress (Box 74)
    - Disasters (Box 74)
    - Education and Labor (Box 74)
    - Energy (Box 74)
    - Environment (Box 74)
    - Foreign Relations (Box 74)
    - Grants (Box 75)
    - Health (Box 75)
    - Housing (Box 75)
    - Immigration (Box 75)
    - Judiciary (Box 75)
    - Military (Box 76)
    - Office Administration (Box 76)
    - Politics (Box 76)
    - Public Relations (Box 76)
    - Science and Technology (Box 76)
    - Social Programs (Box 76)
    - State of Michigan (Box 76)
    - Taxes (Box 76)
    - Transportation (Box 76)
    - Veterans (Box 76)
  - Busing correspondence
    - 1971-1972 (Box 77)
    - 1972-1974 (Box 78)
- Legislative Files 1965-1980, 17 linear feet
  LEGISLATIVE FILES (17 linear feet; 1965-1980) consist of bills, correspondence, memoranda and clippings. They are arranged chronologically by year, and within each year, alphabetically by name of the committee which was responsible for the legislation. Only bills which generated correspondence from colleagues, lobbyists, or constituents, or which were introduced by Ford, have been retained. Where available, compilations of Ford's voting record and "Bills Introduced or Co-sponsored" files have been included with each year's legislative files.
  - 1965-1966
    - Bills Introduced by W.D. Ford (Box 79)
    - Agriculture Committee (Box 79)
    - Appropriations Committee (Box 79)
    - Education and Labor Committee (Box 79)
    - Education and Labor Committee, cont. (Box 80)
    - Judiciary Committee (Box 80)
    - Voting Record (Box 80)
    - Voting Rights Act (Box 80)
  - 1966-1967
    - Agriculture Committee (Box 80)
    - Armed Services Committee (Box 80)
    - Commerce Committee (Box 80)
    - Education and Labor Committee (Box 80)
    - Foreign Assistance Act (Box 80)
    - Judiciary Committee (Box 80)
    - Post Office and Civil Service Committee (Box 80)
    - Vocational Education (Box 80)
    - Ways and Means Committee (Box 80)
    - Legislative correspondence and summaries (Box 81)
      - AFL-CIO Legislative Positions 1967 (Box 81)
      - Committee on Education and Labor Report Summaries 1966 (Box 81)
      - Elementary and Secondary Education Act Amendment 1966 (Box 81)
      - Elementary and Secondary School Construction Act of 1965 (Box 81)
      - Employment Service Act 1967 (Box 81)
      - General Correspondence on Office of Economic Opportunity 1967 (Box 81)
      - Guaranteed Employment Act 1967 (Box 81)
      - Postal Rate correspondence 1967 (Box 81)
    - Legislative Notebooks
      - Economic Opportunity Act Amendments 1966 (Box 81)
      - Job Corps Hearings 1966 (Box 81)
      - Postal Revenue and Federal Salary Act of 1967 (Box 81)
  - 1967-1968
    - Bills Introduced by W.D. Ford (Box 82)
    - Agriculture Committee (Box 82)
    - Appropriations Committee (Box 82)
    - Armed Services Committee (Box 82)
    - Banking and Currency Committee (Box 82)
    - Education and Labor Committee (Box 82)
    - Foreign Affairs Committee (Box 82)
    - House Administration Committee (Box 82)
    - Housing and Urban Development Act of 1968 (Box 82)
    - Interior Committee (Box 82)
    - Judiciary Committee (Box 82)
    - St. Lawrence Seaway (Box 82)
    - Select Committee on Labor (Box 82)
    - Taxation Legislation (Box 82)
    - Travel Restrictions (Box 82)
    - Urban Renewal/ Garden City Legislation (Box 82)
    - Vocational Education (Box 83)
    - Voting Record (Box 83)
    - Ways and Means Committee (Box 83)
  - 1968-1969
    - Appropriations Committee (Box 83)
    - Armed Services Committee (Box 83)
    - Banking and Currency (Box 83)
    - Foreign Affairs Committee (Box 83)
    - Government Operations Committee (Box 83)
    - House Administration Committee (Box 83)
    - Interior Committee (Box 83)
    - Interstate and Foreign Commerce (Box 83)
    - Judiciary Committee (Box 83)
    - Judiciary Committee, cont. (Box 84)
    - Post Office and Civil Service Committee (Box 84)
    - Public Works (Box 84)
    - Veterans Affairs (Box 84)
    - Voting Record (Box 84)
    - Ways and Means Committee (Box 84)
  - 1970-1971
    - Bills introduced or co-sponsored by W.D. Ford (Box 85)
    - Agriculture Committee (Box 85)
    - Appropriations Committee (Box 85)
    - Education and Labor Committee (Box 85)
    - Education and Labor Committee, cont. (Box 86)
    - Foreign Affairs Committee (Box 86)
    - Government Operations Committee (Box 86)
    - Interior Committee (Box 86)
    - Interstate and Foreign Commerce Committee (Box 86)
    - Judiciary Committee (Box 86)
    - Judiciary Committee, cont. (Box 87)
    - Merchant Marine and Fisheries (Box 87)
    - Post Office and Civil Service Committee (Box 87)
    - Public Works Committee (Box 87)
    - Veterans Affairs Committee (Box 87)
    - Voting Record (Box 87)
    - Ways and Means Committee (Box 87)
  - 1971-1972
    - Files, 9 folders (Box 151)
      (files for 1971/72 were received in 1997, arranged alphabetically by House Committee, then by bill number)
  - 1973-1974
    - Bills introduced or co-sponsored by W.D. Ford (Box 88)
    - Agriculture Committee (Box 88)
    - Appropriations Committee (Box 88)
    - Armed Services Committee (Box 88)
    - District of Columbia Legislation (Box 88)
    - Education and Labor Committee (Box 88)
      (the files relating to H.R. 69, The Elementary and Secondary Education Amendments of 1973 were received in 1997 and are located in boxes 151-152 and described on p. 55)
    - Government Operations Committee (Box 88)
    - House Administration (Box 88)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs (Box 89)
    - Interstate and Foreign Commerce (Box 89)
    - Judiciary Committee (Box 89)
    - Merchant Marine and Fisheries (Box 89)
    - Post Office and Civil Service Committee (Box 89)
    - Rules Committee (Box 89)
    - Veterans Affairs Committee (Box 89)
    - Voting Record (Box 89)
    - Ways and Means Committee (Box 89)
  - 1975-1976
    - Agriculture Committee (Box 90)
    - Appropriations Committee (Box 90)
    - Banking and Currency Committee (Box 90)
    - Education and Labor Committee (Box 90)
    - Government Operations Committee (Box 90)
    - House Administration Committee (Box 90)
    - Interstate and Foreign Commerce Committee (Box 90)
    - Judiciary Committee (Box 90)
    - Post Office and Civil Service Committee (Box 91)
    - Public Works Committee (Box 91)
    - Veterans Affairs Committee (Box 91)
    - Voting Record (Box 91)
    - Ways and Means Committee (Box 91)
  - 1977-1978
    - Bills introduced or co-sponsored by W.D. Ford (Box 91)
    - Agriculture Committee (Box 91)
    - Appropriations Committee (Box 91)
    - Armed Services Committee (Box 91)
    - Banking, Finance and Urban Affairs Committee (Box 92)
    - Education and Labor Committee (Box 92)
    - Energy, Ad-hoc Committee (Box 92)
    - Government Operations Committee (Box 92)
    - House Administration Committee (Box 92)
    - Interior and Insular Affairs (Box 93)
    - International Relations (Box 93)
    - Interstate and Foreign Commerce (Box 93)
    - Judiciary Committee (Box 93)
    - Merchant Marine and Fisheries (Box 93)
    - Post Office and Civil Service Committee (Box 93)
    - Public Works and Transportation Committee (Box 93)
    - Rules Committee (Box 93)
    - Science and Technology Committee (Box 93)
    - Veterans Affairs Committee (Box 93)
    - Voting Record (Box 93)
    - Ways and Means Committee (Box 93)
  - 1979-1980
    - Appropriations Committee (Box 94)
    - Armed Services Committee (Box 94)